{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Window Tinting Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40461/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40461,"taskName":"Window Tinting - Apply or Replace","taskDescription":"Apply or Replace Window Tinting","xmTaskDescriptor":"Window Tinting Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":273,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Window Apply mirror glass Tinting","textMessagingName":"Apply Tint","rolloverLongDesc":"Done by specialty window tinting firms \u0026 some window replacement firms. Film can greatly reduce summer cooling costs as well as protect internal furnishings from sunlight.","rolloverShortDesc":"Used to reduce heat gain \u0026 destructive UV light.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply or Replace Window Tinting.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Residential \u0026 Home Window Tinting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Window Tinting","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":38,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Window Tinting Apply or Remove","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Window Tinting - Apply or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Window Tinting Project","urlName":"Window-Tinting-Apply-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Window Tinting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Window,Apply,mirror,glass,Tinting","emcCategoryOid":-12037,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":751,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40461/":{"taskOID":40461,"originalTaskOID":40461,"setID":751,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4889,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Windows","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many windows do you want to apply window tinting to?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200813,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4890,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Tinting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want your windows tinted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5083,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce heat absorption","answerDisplayText":"Reduce heat absorption","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5082,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reduce UV light","answerDisplayText":"Reduce UV light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect furniture, curtains","answerDisplayText":"Protect furniture, curtains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4906,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prevent glare","answerDisplayText":"Prevent glare","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4889,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Windows","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many windows do you want to apply window tinting to?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200813,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10831,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 5","answerDisplayText":"3 - 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10181,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6 - 10","answerDisplayText":"6 - 10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200813,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11+","answerDisplayText":"11+","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4890,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Tinting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want your windows tinted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5083,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce heat absorption","answerDisplayText":"Reduce heat absorption","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5082,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reduce UV light","answerDisplayText":"Reduce UV light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect furniture, curtains","answerDisplayText":"Protect furniture, curtains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4906,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prevent glare","answerDisplayText":"Prevent glare","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Privacy","answerDisplayText":"Privacy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5083,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Reduce heat absorption","answerDisplayText":"Reduce heat absorption","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5082,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reduce UV light","answerDisplayText":"Reduce UV light","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Protect furniture, curtains","answerDisplayText":"Protect furniture, curtains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4906,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prevent glare","answerDisplayText":"Prevent glare","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}